[{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980347449,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":45991,"timeElapsed":171750},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980362629,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":15178,"timeElapsed":186930},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980374424,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":11793,"timeElapsed":198725},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980402457,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":28030,"timeElapsed":226757},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980417264,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":14806,"timeElapsed":241565},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980429444,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":12179,"timeElapsed":253745},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980436675,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":7229,"timeElapsed":260976},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980440180,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":3504,"timeElapsed":264481},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980451976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":11795,"timeElapsed":276277},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980539066,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":85476,"timeElapsed":363367},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980550072,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":11005,"timeElapsed":374373},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980559716,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":9642,"timeElapsed":384017},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980565114,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":5397,"timeElapsed":389415},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980569586,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4471,"timeElapsed":393887},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980572328,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2741,"timeElapsed":396629},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980575696,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":3367,"timeElapsed":399997},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980578726,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3029,"timeElapsed":403027},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980592234,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":13507,"timeElapsed":416535},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980604942,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":10519,"timeElapsed":429243},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980613000,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":8057,"timeElapsed":437301},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980616610,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3609,"timeElapsed":440911},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980622430,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":5819,"timeElapsed":446731},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980626584,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4153,"timeElapsed":450885},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980630082,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3497,"timeElapsed":454383},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980635270,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":5187,"timeElapsed":459571},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980639616,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4345,"timeElapsed":463917},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980646658,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":7041,"timeElapsed":470959},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980651544,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4885,"timeElapsed":475845},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980660410,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":7405,"timeElapsed":484711},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980665564,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":5153,"timeElapsed":489865},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980672966,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":7400,"timeElapsed":497267},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980676396,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3429,"timeElapsed":500697},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980680236,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3839,"timeElapsed":504537},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980682694,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2457,"timeElapsed":506995},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980685614,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2919,"timeElapsed":509915},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980688976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":3361,"timeElapsed":513277},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980691192,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2215,"timeElapsed":515493},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980695650,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3521,"timeElapsed":519951},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980707248,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":11597,"timeElapsed":531549},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980709506,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2257,"timeElapsed":533807},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980711370,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":1863,"timeElapsed":535671},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980713970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2599,"timeElapsed":538271},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980716352,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2381,"timeElapsed":540653},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980721240,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":4887,"timeElapsed":545541},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980725238,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3997,"timeElapsed":549539},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980728672,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":3433,"timeElapsed":552973},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980736887,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":6454,"timeElapsed":561188},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980741440,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":4552,"timeElapsed":565741},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980744552,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":3111,"timeElapsed":568853},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980747344,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":2791,"timeElapsed":571645},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980750214,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2869,"timeElapsed":574515},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980752130,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":1915,"timeElapsed":576431},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980754334,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2203,"timeElapsed":578635},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980756958,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2622,"timeElapsed":581258},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980760712,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3753,"timeElapsed":585013},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980767326,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":5739,"timeElapsed":591627},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980769632,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2305,"timeElapsed":593933},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980771821,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2188,"timeElapsed":596122},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980774706,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":2884,"timeElapsed":599007},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980776978,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2270,"timeElapsed":601279},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980779182,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":2203,"timeElapsed":603483},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980781496,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":2313,"timeElapsed":605797},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980783856,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2359,"timeElapsed":608157},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980786216,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2359,"timeElapsed":610517},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980792094,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":4889,"timeElapsed":616395},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980795572,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":3477,"timeElapsed":619873},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980797848,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2275,"timeElapsed":622149},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980802794,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":4945,"timeElapsed":627095},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980805478,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2683,"timeElapsed":629779},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980808008,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":2529,"timeElapsed":632309},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980814390,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":6381,"timeElapsed":638691},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980816918,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2526,"timeElapsed":641219},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980819670,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2751,"timeElapsed":643971},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980825384,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":4891,"timeElapsed":649685},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980827246,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1861,"timeElapsed":651547},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980834024,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6777,"timeElapsed":658325},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980836572,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2547,"timeElapsed":660873},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980839180,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2607,"timeElapsed":663481},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980841322,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2141,"timeElapsed":665623},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980843258,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":1935,"timeElapsed":667559},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980845394,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2135,"timeElapsed":669695},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980848124,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":2729,"timeElapsed":672425},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980850316,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2191,"timeElapsed":674617},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980865220,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":14144,"timeElapsed":689521},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980867446,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2224,"timeElapsed":691747},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980869882,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":2435,"timeElapsed":694183},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980871618,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":1735,"timeElapsed":695919},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980876204,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":4585,"timeElapsed":700505},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980878376,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2171,"timeElapsed":702677},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980882778,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":4401,"timeElapsed":707079},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980886148,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3369,"timeElapsed":710449},{"subjectID":"fjvgah14s1","prolificID":"673e32bf455c468b0428c1fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235682dc92030cdcc53","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980888540,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":2391,"timeElapsed":712841}]